const qBank = {
  Aaron: [
    {
      question: "What was Lucy June's mom's name?",
      answers: ["Leona", "Eda", "Mildred", "Doris"],
      correct: "Eda",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a brother of Lucy June's?",
      answers: ["Billy", "Frank", "Jack", "Oscar"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What role did Bob serve during the Vietnam War?",
      answers: ["Infantry", "Artillery", "Airforce", "Surveillance"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a brother of Dewey C's?",
      answers: ["Wesley", "Don", "Cooter", "Howard"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a sister of Dewey C's?",
      answers: ["Reba", "Mabel", "Caroline", "Dorothy"],
      correct: "Reba",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not one of Paula's cats?",
      answers: ["Smokey", "Spike", "Molly", "Dusty"],
      correct: "Molly",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Tim's middle name?",
      answers: ["Wayne", "David", "James", "Ronald"],
      correct: "Wayne",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was Dewey C's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 21st", "October 5th", "March 21st", "August 28th"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was grandpa's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 21st", "October 5th", "March 21st", "August 28th"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was Lucy June's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 2nd", "October 17th", "April 9th", "May 12th"],
      correct: "October 17th",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Both Lucy June and Dewey C were born in what year?",
      answers: ["1922", "1925", "1924", "1923"],
      correct: "1923",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Who wore the snakeskin boots?",
      answers: ["Will Corner", "Matt Lippus", "Stan Blatty", "Henry Lash"],
      correct: "Will Corner",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's Sharon's favorite animal?",
      answers: ["Dog", "Giraffe", "Elephant", "Seahorse"],
      correct: "Seahorse",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's Paula's favorite animal?",
      answers: ["Monkey", "Dog", "Cat", "Horse"],
      correct: "Monkey",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What country did Beverly always dream about going to?",
      answers: ["Italy", "France", "England", "Germany"],
      correct: "France",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Uncle Dick's real name?",
      answers: ["Virgil", "Richard", "Chester", "Eugene"],
      correct: "Virgil",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When is Jeff's birthday?",
      answers: ["April 8th", "December 12th", "March 9th", "Marth 29th"],
      correct: "April 8th",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's only real brother's name?",
      answers: ["Donald", "Dennis", "Howard", "Jack"],
      correct: "Donald",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Dewey C was honorably discharged from the Air Force due to what condition?",
      answers: ["Anxiety", "Arthiritis", "Depression", "Asthma"],
      correct: "Asthma",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sonia (Bonnie)'s current last name?",
      answers: ["Parrish", "James", "Smith", "Curlington"],
      correct: "Parrish",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sonia (Bonnie)'s husband's name?",
      answers: ["Elijah", "Will", "Lucas", "Raymond"],
      correct: "Asthma",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Skeeter's dog's name?",
      answers: ["Henry", "Ziggy", "Herbert", "Chico"],
      correct: "Ziggy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What did Isara major in at MTSU?",
      answers: ["Sociology", "Philosophy", "Art", "Music Theory"],
      correct: "Philosophy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Isara took which martial arts as a teenager?",
      answers: ["Karate", "Boxing", "Jiu-Jitsu", "Taekwondo"],
      correct: "Taekwondo",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Isara's band's name?",
      answers: [
        "When Sleeping Fails",
        "Today for Tomorrow",
        "Shun",
        "Blowin' Mud",
      ],
      correct: "When Sleeping Fails",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What sport did Isara do during highschool?",
      answers: ["Rock Climbing", "Soccer", "Wrestling", "Golf"],
      correct: "Taekwondo",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What instrument did Isara play when he was younger?",
      answers: ["Guitar", "Drums", "Bass", "Electric Triangle"],
      correct: "Bass",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was the maximum number of cars Jeff had at one time?",
      answers: ["19", "35", "51", "28"],
      correct: "28",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not one of Jeff's cars?",
      answers: [
        "1969 Chevy Camaro",
        "1964 Grand Prix",
        "1970 Pontiac Can Am",
        "1969 GTO",
      ],
      correct: "1969 Chevy Camaro",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's last car?",
      answers: [
        "1975 Pontiac Catalina",
        "1977 Pontiac Boneville",
        "1979 Pontiac Trans Am",
        "1978 Pontiac Phoenix",
      ],
      correct: "1977 Pontiac Boneville",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
  ],
  Maw: [
    {
      question:
        "What object did dad beat Isara with for not letting Yo play Nintendo?",
      answers: ["Belt", "Chain of Pain", "Pooper Scooper", "Nunchucks"],
      correct: "Pooper Scooper",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Jimbob's last name?",
      answers: ["Jimbob", "Johnson", "Hermon", "Castillo"],
      correct: "Hermon",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Yo's favorite food?",
      answers: ["Cheeseburger", "Steak", "Sashimi", "Pad Thai"],
      correct: "Sashimi",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Skeeter's favorite food?",
      answers: ["Tacos", "Okra", "Medium rare steak", "Pad Thai"],
      correct: "Tacos",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "How did Yo break his leg when he was a kid?",
      answers: ["Soccer", "Swimming Pool", "Knife Fight", "Hide and Go Seek"],
      correct: "Hide and Go Seek",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What city in China did Yo live in for 1 year?",
      answers: ["Shanghai", "Guangzhou", "Beijing", "Hangzhou"],
      correct: "Mrs.Orr",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Skeeter's lizard's name?",
      answers: ["Herbert", "Hanson", "Harry", "Harvey"],
      correct: "Herbert",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Wesley (Yo's friend)'s wife's name?",
      answers: ["Megan", "Samantha", "Raven", "Morgan"],
      correct: "Megan",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "How many times did Yo have to take Algebra II?",
      answers: ["1", "2", "3", "0"],
      correct: "3",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Eli (Yo's friend)'s mom's sister's name?",
      answers: ["Joanna", "Janice", "Julia", "Janet"],
      correct: "Janet",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Jimbob's wife's name?",
      answers: ["Jimbob", "Danielle", "Abby", "Chloe"],
      correct: "Hermon",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which of the following was a former lead singer of When Sleeping Fails"?',
      answers: ["Todd", "John", "Daniel", "Sam"],
      correct: "Todd",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was BB's first name (English)?",
      answers: ["Calissa", "Lin", "Vivian", "Carol"],
      correct: "Calissa",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the name of the first online monthly payment game Yo played?",
      answers: ["World of Warcraft", "Oculus", "Google", "Final Fantasy 11"],
      correct: "Final Fantasy 11",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not one of Joyce's kids",
      answers: ["Fred", "Robert", "John", "Archie"],
      correct: "John",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Natasha's last name?",
      answers: ["Roberts", "Collins", "Johnson", "Richardson"],
      correct: "Collins",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is dad's favorite country music singers?",
      answers: ["Kenny Rogers", "Bobby Bare", "Willy Nelson", "Conway Twitty"],
      correct: "Bobby Bare",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is the name of one of Steven's brothers?",
      answers: ["Dustin", "David", "Derrick", "Dilan"],
      correct: "David",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's Daniel's (Steve's brother) son's name?",
      answers: ["Cameron", "Dillon", "Nathan", "Brock"],
      correct: "Cameron",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "What's the name of the girl that got your hair tangled in a brush?",
      answers: ["Tiffany", "Jessica", "Lauren", "Leah"],
      correct: "Leah",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's Kyle's sister's name?",
      answers: ["Teresa", "Tiffany", "Taylor", "Tessa"],
      correct: "Tiffany",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's Steve's girlfriend's name?",
      answers: ["Ashley", "Morgan", "Emma", "Laura"],
      correct: "Morgan",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Big Sister's real name?",
      answers: ["Pachanee", "Chantana", "Charanya", "Tansanee"],
      correct: "Pachanee",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Yo's friend Sergei's last name?",
      answers: ["Katsuba", "Ivanov", "Belandin", "Popov"],
      correct: "Katsuba",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the name of the Coding Bootcamp Yo attended in Malaysia?",
      answers: [
        "KL Software School",
        "Fullstack Academy",
        "Flatiron School",
        "Next Academy",
      ],
      correct: "Next Academy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What city did Yo live in in Malaysia?",
      answers: ["George Town", "Kuala Lumpur", "Kota Kinabalu", "Kuching"],
      correct: "Kuala Lumpur",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's Daniel's (Steve's brother) son's name?",
      answers: ["Cameron", "Dillon", "Nathan", "Brock"],
      correct: "Cameron",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's Daniel's (Steve's brother) son's name?",
      answers: ["Cameron", "Dillon", "Nathan", "Brock"],
      correct: "Cameron",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was one of Isara's dreams growing up?",
      answers: [
        "Open a video game store with Micah",
        "Survive in the wilderness for 1 week alone",
        "Live in Germany",
        "Start activity camp for kids with Diabetes",
      ],
      correct: "Start activity camp for kids with Diabetes",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which foreign language did Yo study in high school?",
      answers: ["German", "Spanish", "Chinese", "Latin"],
      correct: "German",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which foreign language did Isara study in high school?",
      answers: ["French", "Spanish", "German", "Latin"],
      correct: "German",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
  ],
  Isara: [
    {
      question: "How many (half) siblings did Dewey C have?",
      answers: ["5", "4", "6", "7"],
      correct: "5",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What role did Bob serve during the Vietnam War?",
      answers: ["Infantry", "Artillery", "Airforce", "Surveillance"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Bob's middle name?",
      answers: ["Robert", "Eugene", "Charles", "Dwight"],
      correct: "Eugene",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which foreign language did Yo study in high school?",
      answers: ["German", "Spanish", "Chinese", "Latin"],
      correct: "German",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not one of Jeff's cars?",
      answers: [
        "1969 Chevy Camaro",
        "1964 Grand Prix",
        "1970 Pontiac Can Am",
        "1969 GTO",
      ],
      correct: "1969 Chevy Camaro",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was the maximum number of cars Jeff had at one time?",
      answers: ["19", "35", "51", "28"],
      correct: "28",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What year did mom and dad get married?",
      answers: [
        "June 6th, 1971",
        "June 9th, 1970",
        "July 6th, 1971",
        "July 10th, 1970",
      ],
      correct: "June 6th, 1971",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Dewey C was honorably discharged from the Air Force due to what condition?",
      answers: ["Anxiety", "Arthiritis", "Depression", "Asthma"],
      correct: "Asthma",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's only real brother's name?",
      answers: ["Donald", "Dennis", "Howard", "Jack"],
      correct: "Donald",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a brother of Dewey C's?",
      answers: ["Wesley", "Don", "Cooter", "Howard"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's last car?",
      answers: [
        "1975 Pontiac Catalina",
        "1977 Pontiac Boneville",
        "1979 Pontiac Trans Am",
        "1978 Pontiac Phoenix",
      ],
      correct: "1977 Pontiac Boneville",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a sister of Dewey C's?",
      answers: ["Reba", "Mabel", "Caroline", "Dorothy"],
      correct: "Reba",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was Dewey C's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 21st", "October 5th", "March 21st", "August 28th"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was grandpa's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 21st", "October 5th", "March 21st", "August 28th"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was Lucy June's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 2nd", "October 17th", "April 9th", "May 12th"],
      correct: "October 17th",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Both Lucy June and Dewey C were born in what year?",
      answers: ["1922", "1925", "1924", "1923"],
      correct: "1923",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a brother of Lucy June's?",
      answers: ["Billy", "Frank", "Jack", "Oscar"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Lucy June's mom's name?",
      answers: ["Leona", "Eda", "Mildred", "Doris"],
      correct: "Eda",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Jimbob's last name?",
      answers: ["Jimbob", "Johnson", "Hermon", "Castillo"],
      correct: "Hermon",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's real mother's name?",
      answers: ["Mildred", "Anne", "Leona", "Rose"],
      correct: "Mildred",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the Beatles is mom's favorite?",
      answers: [
        "John Lennon",
        "Paul McCartney",
        "Ringo Starr",
        "George Harrison",
      ],
      correct: "Paul McCartney",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "How to say delicious in Thai?",
      answers: ["Law", "Mak", "Suay", "Arroy"],
      correct: "Arroy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of dad's friends did dad go with for mom and dad's first date?",
      answers: ["Sim", "Padet", "Bobby", "Woody"],
      correct: "Sim",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of mom's friends did mom go with for mom and dad's first date?",
      answers: ["Rhonda", "Shirley", "Sandy", "Shelly"],
      correct: "Shelly",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the name of Yo's Japanese friend in Thailand who we partied with and hung out with?",
      answers: ["Kosuke", "Taku", "Hiro", "Makoto"],
      correct: "Makoto",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's the name of Aaron's current girlfriend?",
      answers: ["Lucy", "Rubi", "Maria", "Carmen"],
      correct: "Lucy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Susan's last name?",
      answers: ["Vaughn", "Woods", "Sandy", "Makoto"],
      correct: "Woods",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sharon's middle name?",
      answers: ["Dorothy", "Barbara", "Diane", "Evelyn"],
      correct: "Diane",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is dad's nickname?",
      answers: ["Pi", "Moo", "Lek", "Sia"],
      correct: "Sia",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "How many siblings did dad originally have total (including himself)?",
      answers: ["5", "7", "4", "6"],
      correct: "7",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the nickname of dad's little brother who had down syndrome?",
      answers: ["Kob", "Lek", "Bet", "Ek"],
      correct: "Bet",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Hannah's last name?",
      answers: ["Kincaid", "Brown", "Stocking", "Cameron"],
      correct: "Kincaid",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Nitnoy's son's name?",
      answers: ["Johnny", "Dillon", "Chandler", "Cameron"],
      correct: "Chandler",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "How many siblings does Steve have?",
      answers: ["3", "4", "2", "1"],
      correct: "2",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was dad's dad's real name?",
      answers: ["Ah Gong", "Jing Lee", "Juan Lee", "Bek Tang"],
      correct: "Bek Tang",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sonia (Bonnie)'s current last name?",
      answers: ["Parrish", "James", "Smith", "Curlington"],
      correct: "Parrish",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sonia (Bonnie)'s husband's name?",
      answers: ["Elijah", "Will", "Lucas", "Raymond"],
      correct: "Asthma",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When is Emil's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 8th", "October 2nd", "August 21st", "February 20th"],
      correct: "September 8th",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When is Aaron's birthday?",
      answers: ["October 8th", "October 7th", "November 4th", "September 21st"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
  ],
  Skeeter: [
    {
      question: "How many (half) siblings did Dewey C have?",
      answers: ["5", "4", "6", "7"],
      correct: "7",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What role did Bob serve during the Vietnam War?",
      answers: ["Infantry", "Artillery", "Airforce", "Surveillance"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Bob's middle name?",
      answers: ["Robert", "Eugene", "Charles", "Dwight"],
      correct: "Eugene",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not one of Jeff's cars?",
      answers: [
        "1969 Chevy Camaro",
        "1964 Grand Prix",
        "1970 Pontiac Can Am",
        "1969 GTO",
      ],
      correct: "1969 Chevy Camaro",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When is Emil's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 8th", "October 2nd", "August 21st", "February 20th"],
      correct: "September 8th",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When is Aaron's birthday?",
      answers: ["October 8th", "October 7th", "November 4th", "September 21st"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was the maximum number of cars Jeff had at one time?",
      answers: ["19", "35", "51", "28"],
      correct: "28",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's last car?",
      answers: [
        "1975 Pontiac Catalina",
        "1977 Pontiac Boneville",
        "1979 Pontiac Trans Am",
        "1978 Pontiac Phoenix",
      ],
      correct: "1977 Pontiac Boneville",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which teacher of Isara's hated Isara and put him in ISS?",
      answers: ["Mrs.Wildred", "Mrs.Odom", "Mrs.Lee", "Mrs.Donohugh"],
      correct: "Mrs.Wildred",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What year did mom and dad get married?",
      answers: [
        "June 6th, 1971",
        "June 9th, 1970",
        "July 6th, 1971",
        "July 10th, 1970",
      ],
      correct: "June 6th, 1971",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sonia (Bonnie)'s current last name?",
      answers: ["Parrish", "James", "Smith", "Curlington"],
      correct: "Parrish",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sonia (Bonnie)'s husband's name?",
      answers: ["Elijah", "Will", "Lucas", "Raymond"],
      correct: "Asthma",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was dad's dad's real name?",
      answers: ["Ah Gong", "Jing Lee", "Juan Lee", "Bek Tang"],
      correct: "Bek Tang",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Dewey C was honorably discharged from the Air Force due to what condition?",
      answers: ["Anxiety", "Arthiritis", "Depression", "Asthma"],
      correct: "Asthma",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's only real brother's name?",
      answers: ["Donald", "Dennis", "Howard", "Jack"],
      correct: "Donald",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's only real brother's name?",
      answers: ["Donald", "Dennis", "Howard", "Jack"],
      correct: "Donald",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a brother of Dewey C's?",
      answers: ["Wesley", "Don", "Cooter", "Howard"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a sister of Dewey C's?",
      answers: ["Reba", "Mabel", "Caroline", "Dorothy"],
      correct: "Reba",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was Dewey C's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 21st", "October 5th", "March 21st", "August 28th"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was grandpa's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 21st", "October 5th", "March 21st", "August 28th"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was Lucy June's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 2nd", "October 17th", "April 9th", "May 12th"],
      correct: "October 17th",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Both Lucy June and Dewey C were born in what year?",
      answers: ["1922", "1925", "1924", "1923"],
      correct: "1923",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a brother of Lucy June's?",
      answers: ["Billy", "Frank", "Jack", "Oscar"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Lucy June's mom's name?",
      answers: ["Leona", "Eda", "Mildred", "Doris"],
      correct: "Eda",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's real mother's name?",
      answers: ["Mildred", "Anne", "Leona", "Rose"],
      correct: "Mildred",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the Beatles is mom's favorite?",
      answers: [
        "John Lennon",
        "Paul McCartney",
        "Ringo Starr",
        "George Harrison",
      ],
      correct: "Paul McCartney",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "How to say delicious in Thai?",
      answers: ["Law", "Mak", "Suay", "Arroy"],
      correct: "HTC",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of dad's friends did dad go with for mom and dad's first date?",
      answers: ["Sim", "Padet", "Bobby", "Woody"],
      correct: "Sim",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of mom's friends did mom go with for mom and dad's first date?",
      answers: ["Rhonda", "Shirley", "Sandy", "Shelly"],
      correct: "Shelly",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the name of Yo's Japanese friend in Thailand who we partied with and hung out with?",
      answers: ["Kosuke", "Taku", "Hiro", "Makoto"],
      correct: "Makoto",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What's the name of Aaron's current girlfriend?",
      answers: ["Lucy", "Rubi", "Maria", "Carmen"],
      correct: "Lucy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },

    {
      question: "What is Susan's last name?",
      answers: ["Vaughn", "Woods", "Sandy", "Makoto"],
      correct: "Woods",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sharon's middle name?",
      answers: ["Dorothy", "Barbara", "Danielle", "Evelyn"],
      correct: "Danielle",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is dad's nickname?",
      answers: ["Dorothy", "Barbara", "Danielle", "Sia"],
      correct: "Sia",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "How many siblings did dad originally have total (including himself)?",
      answers: ["5", "7", "4", "6"],
      correct: "Danielle",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "What was the nickname of dad's little brother who had down syndrome?",
      answers: ["Kob", "Lek", "Bet", "Ek"],
      correct: "Bet",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Beverly's favorite animal?",
      answers: ["Giraffe", "Dog", "Elephant", "Pig"],
      correct: "Elephant",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Rhonda's favorite animal?",
      answers: ["Dog", "Pig", "Giraffe", "Monkey"],
      correct: "Pig",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Dewey C was honorably discharged from the Air Force due to what condition?",
      answers: ["Anxiety", "Arthiritis", "Depression", "Asthma"],
      correct: "Asthma",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
  ],
  Sharon: [
    {
      question:
        "What's the name of Paula's friend who she had the wreck with when she was 16?",
      answers: ["Debby Jones", "Carole Hale", "Vonda Bozarth", "Debby Osmond"],
      correct: "Carole Hale",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What role did Bob serve during the Vietnam War?",
      answers: ["Infantry", "Artillery", "Airforce", "Surveillance"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not one of Jeff's cars?",
      answers: [
        "1969 Chevy Camaro",
        "1964 Grand Prix",
        "1970 Pontiac Can Am",
        "1969 GTO",
      ],
      correct: "1969 Chevy Camaro",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was the maximum number of cars Jeff had at one time?",
      answers: ["19", "35", "51", "28"],
      correct: "28",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not one of Paula's cats?",
      answers: ["Smokey", "Spike", "Molly", "Dusty"],
      correct: "Molly",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's last car?",
      answers: [
        "1975 Pontiac Catalina",
        "1977 Pontiac Boneville",
        "1979 Pontiac Trans Am",
        "1978 Pontiac Phoenix",
      ],
      correct: "1977 Pontiac Boneville",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What year did Paula and Peter get married?",
      answers: [
        "June 6th, 1971",
        "June 9th, 1970",
        "July 6th, 1971",
        "July 10th, 1970",
      ],
      correct: "June 6th, 1971",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sonia (Bonnie)'s husband's name?",
      answers: ["Elijah", "Will", "Lucas", "Raymond"],
      correct: "Asthma",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Sonia (Bonnie)'s current last name?",
      answers: ["Parrish", "James", "Smith", "Curlington"],
      correct: "Parrish",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's only real brother's name?",
      answers: ["Donald", "Dennis", "Howard", "Jack"],
      correct: "Donald",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a brother of Dewey C's?",
      answers: ["Wesley", "Don", "Cooter", "Howard"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a sister of Dewey C's?",
      answers: ["Reba", "Mabel", "Caroline", "Dorothy"],
      correct: "Reba",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was Dewey C's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 21st", "October 5th", "March 21st", "August 28th"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was grandpa's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 21st", "October 5th", "March 21st", "August 28th"],
      correct: "September 21st",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When was Lucy June's birthday?",
      answers: ["September 2nd", "October 17th", "April 9th", "May 12th"],
      correct: "October 17th",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Both Lucy June and Dewey C were born in what year?",
      answers: ["1922", "1925", "1924", "1923"],
      correct: "1923",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following was not a brother of Lucy June's?",
      answers: ["Billy", "Frank", "Jack", "Oscar"],
      correct: "Jack",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Lucy June's mom's name?",
      answers: ["Leona", "Eda", "Mildred", "Doris"],
      correct: "Eda",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's real mother's name?",
      answers: ["Mildred", "Anne", "Leona", "Rose"],
      correct: "Mildred",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was Dewey C's father's first wife's name?",
      answers: ["Susie", "Anne", "Leona", "Mildred"],
      correct: "Susie",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What instrument did Isara play when he was younger?",
      answers: ["Guitar", "Drums", "Bass", "Electric Triangle"],
      correct: "Bass",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Lucy's last name?",
      answers: ["Hernandez", "Brown", "Martinez", "Brandon"],
      correct: "Brandon",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "How old was Cousin Tim when he appeared on Christina's Court?",
      answers: ["29", "30", "32", "33"],
      correct: "29",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following countries has Yo never lived in?",
      answers: ["China", "Japan", "Malaysia", "Taiwan"],
      correct: "Japan",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "When is Isara's birthday?",
      answers: ["June 23rd", "April 27th", "July 3rd", "March 5th"],
      correct: "July 3rd",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What university did Peter(Yo's dad) study at?",
      answers: ["Vanderbilt", "UT", "Belmont", "Austin Peay"],
      correct: "Belmont",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not a current or past girlfriend of Skeeter?",
      answers: ["Anne Marie", "Mary", "Kim", "Hannah"],
      correct: "Mary",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What did Yo study at university in Taiwan?",
      answers: [
        "Computer Science",
        "Business Management",
        "International Relations",
        "Chinese",
      ],
      correct: "Business Management",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Didi's husband's name",
      answers: ["Kevin", "Clay", "John", "David"],
      correct: "Kevin",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Jeff's favorite color?",
      answers: ["Teal", "Yellow", "Orange", "Green"],
      correct: "Yellow",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What is Hannah (Skeeter's girlfriend)'s last name?",
      answers: ["Kincaid", "Brown", "Stocking", "Cameron"],
      correct: "Kincaid",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was O.C. Junior's nickname?",
      answers: ["Cooter", "Bubba", "Buddy", "Bunt"],
      correct: "Bunt",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question:
        'Who said that she would "marry Tony or else" when they were kids?',
      answers: ["Sherry", "Donna", "Barbara", "Elizabeth"],
      correct: "Sherry",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What did Isara major in at MTSU?",
      answers: ["Sociology", "Philosophy", "Art", "Music Theory"],
      correct: "Philosophy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "What was the name of the mouse at Tony's place in Memphis?",
      answers: ["Varmit", "Jerry", "Hermon", "Stewart"],
      correct: "Philosophy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Who was Beverly's first boyfriend?",
      answers: ["Sunny", "Boton", "Jerry", "Stan"],
      correct: "Sunny",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Who was Beverly's first boyfriend?",
      answers: ["Sunny", "Boton", "Jerry", "Stan"],
      correct: "Philosophy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
    {
      question: "Who was Ronnie's firsst girlfriend?",
      answers: ["Debbie", "Sandy", "Donna", "Sherry"],
      correct: "Sandy",
      questionId: Math.floor(100000 + Math.random() * 900000),
    },
  ],
};
export default (chosenCharacter) =>
  Promise.resolve(
    qBank[chosenCharacter].sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, 5)
  );
